kyero.com 2019-04-17

# Kyero.com Privacy policy. Updated 24-5-2018

### Updated 24-5-2018

### Related: terms and conditions | cookie policy | refund policy

We know that you care how information about you is used, stored and shared and we appreciate your trust in us to do that carefully and sensibly. 

We acknowledge and agree that any of your personal data will be processed in accordance with all applicable data protection laws. By using Kyero.com, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

As far as is reasonably possible, we will ensure all data is:

  * processed lawfully, fairly and in a transparent manner
  * collected for specified, explicit and legitimate purposes
  * adequate, relevant and not excessive
  * accurate and up to date
  * not kept for longer than necessary
  * processed in accordance with your rights
  * secure  

For us to carry out our services, we will ask for your consent to process your data when necessary, and you have the right to withdraw this consent at any time.

This policy applies to any website we own, such as www.kyero.com, and other interactions you may have with us. If you do not agree with the terms, please do not access or use our services.

## Who are we?

Kyero.com, www.kyero.com, or Kyero is the website or commercial name of Portal 47 Limited, a UK registered company that acts as a controller or processor of your information. Our address is Suite 157, 3 Edgar Buildings, George Street, Bath, BA1 2FJ, England (EU VAT registered as GB974515005).

Kyero.com is not an estate agent, we are the providers of the website www.kyero.com. We run this site in order to promote the properties and services of individual estate agents or companies (advertisers), to be the link between you and the advertisers, who may have their own privacy policies which you should also look at.

## What information do we collect?

### Personal data

While using Kyero.com, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that may include, but is not limited to:

  * contact information, such as name, email address or phone number
  * unique Identifiers, such as an account number
  * geo location based on IP address

### Tracking data

Like most websites, we also gather certain information automatically. This information may include:

Internet protocol (IP) addresses, device and browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, the pages viewed on our site, operating system, date/time stamps, and/or other data to analyse trends and administer the site.

Kyero uses cookies or similar technologies to analyse trends, track movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base. You can control the use of cookies at browser level, but if you choose to disable cookies, it may limit your use of certain features or functions on our website or service. For more details about how we use these technologies, please see our cookie policy.

### Additional data

Other data submitted to our websites, such as if you participate in a survey, apply for a job, request support, interact with our social media accounts or otherwise communicate with Kyero, may also be stored.

No one is under any obligation to provide any Additional data. However, you might not be able to make use of some of the features at Kyero.com.

## How do we use the data we receive?

### With Third Parties

When you make an enquiry on Kyero.com, we send that request and share your information with the estate agent advertising the property. 

### With Service Providers

We may share your information with third parties who provide services on our behalf to help with our business activities. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us, to which these services may include:

  * providing customer service
  * sending marketing communications
  * conducting research and analysis
  * analytics
  * payment processing

### With Public Authorities

In certain situations, we might have to release account and other personal information to comply with law, to enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements or to protect the rights, property or safety of Kyero.com, our users or others. This does not include selling, renting, sharing or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information for commercial purposes other than those stated in this policy.

## What data do we store?

We store your data on secure servers provided by our service partners and will hold your personal information on our systems for as long as is necessary for the relevant activity.

Kyero may retain Personal, Tracking or Additional data pertaining to you for as long as necessary for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. This may include keeping information after you have deactivated your account for the period of time needed to pursue legitimate business interests, conduct audits, comply with (and demonstrate compliance with) legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.

Sending information over the internet is generally not completely secure, and we can’t guarantee the security of your data while it’s in transit. We have procedures and security features in place to keep your data secure once we receive it. 

## Your rights

Your rights will be respected and acted upon when invoked, those rights include:

  * the right to be informed
  * the right of access
  * the right to rectification
  * the right to erasure
  * the right to restrict processing
  * the right to data portability
  * the right to object
  * rights related to automated decision making and profiling

We will use all reasonable efforts consistent with our legal duty to supply, correct or delete personal information about you as necessary. Please [make those requests using this form](https://guides.kyero.com/en/data-protection-request) or email us at privacy@kyero.com

Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.

## Age limitations

To the extent prohibited by applicable law, Kyero.com does not offer its services to anyone younger than 16 years old. If you learn that anyone younger than 16 has unlawfully provided us with personal data, please contact us and we will delete that information.

## Changes to this policy

This policy may be updated from time to time, so you may wish to check it each time you submit personal information to Kyero.com. The date of the most recent revisions will appear on this page. If you do not agree to these changes, please do not continue to use this website or submit personal information to it. If material changes are made to the policy, we will provide a more prominent notice, such as by email notification of the changes.

## Data protection authority

Subject to applicable law, you also have the right to lodge a complaint with your local data protection authority or the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO), which is the Kyero.com supervisory authority in the European Union:

Information Commissioner's Office Wycliffe House, Water Lane, Wilmslow, Cheshire, SK9 5AF Tel: +44 (0)303 123 1113 (local rate) or +44(0)1625 545 745 (national rate) Email: casework@ico.org.uk

## Contacting Kyero.com

If you have any concerns about privacy at Kyero.com, please [open a support ticket](https://help.kyero.com/) or email privacy@kyero.com and we will try to resolve it.
